godrejinterio.com 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy Godrej & Boyce Mfg. Ltd. respect your privacy and is committed to protecting it through Company’s compliance with this privacy policy. This policy describes:

Privacy Policy
Godrej & Boyce Mfg. Ltd. respect your privacy and is committed to protecting it through Company’s
compliance with this privacy policy. This policy describes:
    •    the types of information that Company may collect from you when you access or use of RMC
         mobile applications, websites and other online platforms (collectively, "Platforms"); and
    •    Company’s practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.
Note:
By visiting this Platform, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you
do not agree please do not use or access the Platforms.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Service.
This policy DOES NOT apply to information that you provide to, or that is collected by, any third-party,
such as merchants from which you purchase and/or pay and social networks that you use in connection
withCompany’sservices. Company encourages you to consult directly with such third-parties about their
privacy practices.
Information which are collected by us
Company collects this information:
    •    directly or indirectly from you when you provide it to us; and/or
    •    as you navigate through the Platforms (information collected automatically may include usage
         details, IP addresses, location and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other
         tracking technologies via web or mobile).
    •    Through third-party sign-in services including but not limited to Facebook, twitter, Instagram and
         Google Plus. If you use an integrated social media feature on Company’s websites. The third-party
         social media site will give us certain information about you. This could include yourname, email
         address and other personal details.
Information You Provide to Us
The Information Company collects on or through the Platforms shall include inter alia:
    •    Your full name, address, email address, telephone number, date of birth and any proof of your
         identity and/or address, postal code, profile picture, password and other information you may
         provide with your account such as your gender, mobile phone number and website and all other
         information, you may provide us through third-party sign-in services such as Facebook and Google
         Plus etc.. In such events/ cases, Company fetches and stores whatever information is made
         available to us by you through these sign-in services;
    •    Your preferences including settings such as time zone and language;
    •    Details of credit, debit or other card used by You for transactions;

    •    Details of Your visits to Platform, including but not limited to, location data, web logs and other
         communication data;
    •    transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or
         download or use applications or browsing details, contact or notification information, and other
         information in your account profile;
    •    Your search details such as search terms you have looked up and results you selected;
    •    Your browsing details including time, frequency, features used, etc. by you;
    •    Communications between you and other users or merchants through the Platforms; participation
         by you in a survey, poll, sweepstakes, contest or promotion scheme; your request for certain
         features (e.g., newsletters, updates or other products); your communication with us about
         employment opportunities posted;
    •    Information you enter into our system when using the Platform, such as contact information and
         project management information.
    •    Information collected through cookies.
Information received from Third Parties
Company will be collecting, processing and storing your user ID associated with any social media account
(such as your Facebook and Google account) that you use to sign into the Platform or connect with or use
the Platform.
Also, information will be collected about you from third parties such as partners, marketers, third-party
websites, and researchers.
Information Collected Through Platforms
Information may be collected automatically from the computer or devices (including mobile devices) you
use to access the Platforms, even if you use the Platforms without registering or logging in and the same
shall include inter alia:
    •    Your server’s IP address from where the Platform is being accessed, the type of browser (Internet
         Explorer, Firefox, Opera, Google Chrome etc.), the operating system of Your system and the
         website you last visited before visiting to Platform, and your computer, Internet connection and
         mobile device, other browsing information (connection, speed, connection type etc.), device type,
         device’s unique device identifier, mobile network information and the device’s telephone
         number;
    •    Details of your use of the Platforms, including location data, traffic data, logs and other
         communication data and the resources that you use and access on or through the Platforms;
    •    Company also may access metadata and other information associated with other files stored on
         your mobile device. This may include, for example, photographs, audio and video clips, personal
         contacts and address book information;

    •    Company may also collect real-time information about the location of your device, as permitted
         by you;
    •    Unique mobile device identifier (e.g. IDFA or other device IDs on Apple devices like the iPhone
         and iPad), if you’re using the Platforms on a mobile device, Company may use mobile device IDs
         (the unique identifier assigned to a device by the manufacturer), instead of cookies, to recognize
         you. Unlike cookies, mobile device IDs cannot be deleted from records. Company may share it
         with advertising companies and they may use device IDs to track your use of Company’s
         applications, track the number of advertisements displayed, measure advertising performance
         and display advertisements that are more relevant to you. Company may also share it with
         analytics companies which may use mobile device IDs to track your usage of Company’s
         applications;
    •    Other information relating to your activity on the Platforms, such as your search queries,
         comments, domain names, search results selected, number of clicks, pages viewed and the order
         of those pages, how long you visited the Platforms, the date and time you used the Platforms,
         error logs, and other similar information;
    •    Your locations details including the latitude, longitude or altitude of your mobile device, GPS
         location;
    •    In case of mobile application users, the online or offline status of your application.
Other tools and Cookies
Company and third parties with whom Company partners, shall use pixel tags, cookies, web beacons,
mobile device IDs, “flash cookies” and similar files or technologies to collect and store information in
respect to your use of and third party websites and the Platforms. A cookie can be understood as a small
text file that is stored on your computer/ mobile that enables us to recognize you (for example, as a
registered user) when you visit the Platform, website, store your preferences and settings, enhance your
experience by delivering content and advertising specific to your interests, perform research and
analytics, track your use of the Platforms, and assist with security and administrative functions. A pixel tag
(also called a web beacon) can be understood as a small graphic with embedded invisibly on a webpage
(or an online ad or email) and a unique identifier, and is used to count or track things like activity on a
webpage or ad impressions or clicks, as well as to access cookies stored on users’ computers.
Kindly note that most browsers are set to automatically allow cookies. However, kindly note that it may
be possible to disable some (but not all) cookies through yourmobile device or browser settings, but
doing so may interfere with certain functionality on the Platform. Separately, Company advises you to
check their privacy policies for information about third parties cookies and other practices. Company does
not control the practices of such third parties/ partners and their privacy policies/ cookies policies, which
govern their interactions with you.
Anonymous or De-Identified Data
Company may anonymize and/or de-identify information collected from you through the Platform or via
other means, including via the use of third-party web analytic tools as described below. As a result,

Company’s use and disclosure of aggregated and/or de-identified information is not restricted by this
Privacy Policy, and it may be used and disclosed to others without limitation.
Use and disclosure of information collected
Usages
Information collected from you can be used for various purposes including inter alia:
    •   Facilitate your usage of Platform;
    •   To Provide you with the products ordered by you
    •   To process and respond to your queries/ requests;
    •   To inform you regarding changes in Platform;
    •   To analyze, conduct internal reviews, surveys and understand Company’s users, improve the
        content and features of Company’s Platform, process and complete your transactions, and make
        special offers;
    •   To diagnose technical problems and provide support;
    •   To send and receive communications, show advertisements, notifications;
    •   To prepare reports, review, etc.;
    •   To contact you regarding third party goods and services, offers, to understand your preferences,
        requirements;
    •   To permit you to participate in interactive features offered through Company’s Platform;
    •   To detect and protect any error, hacking, fraud, commercial and identity checks; and
    •   Any other purpose as required in connection with the Platform.
Disclosures
Information collected from you may be disclosed to and/ or for various purposes including inter alia:
    •   For legal purposes, requirements, to comply with applicable laws;
    •   To Company’s affiliates, subsidiaries and related parties;
    •   To Company’s vendors, merchants, contractors, service providers and other third-parties and
        persons who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and
        use it only for the purposes for which Company disclose it to them;
    •   Any person for maintaining security, operating Platforms, to enquire or protect from any fraud,
        hacking;
    •   To third-parties to market their products or services to you;
    •   For any other purpose in connection with the aforesaid;

    •    For enforcing or applying Company’s terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and
         collection purposes;
    •    If the disclosure, in Company’s belief, is necessary or appropriate to protect Company’s rights,
         property, or safety, customers or others. This will include exchanging information with other
         companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; and
    •    To help us serve better.
    •    For reasons not described in the policy, Company would notify you about the same before making
         any disclosure.
Email opt-out and account closure
You may choose to stop the receipt of Company’s promotional emails by emailing your request to opt-out
through the link provided in the email. Your request would be processed within 10 working days from
date of receipt. Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, Company will, if applicable, be sending
you transactional messages through email and SMS about your purchases
You can close your account by visiting your profile settings page on Company’s website. Company will
remove your public posts from view and/or dissociate them from your account profile, but Company may
retain information about you for the purposes authorized under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by
law. If you delete your information from Company’s Platforms, copies of your information may remain
viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other users of Company’s
websites/ servers. Platform does not guarantee the complete wiping of any user-data from its servers or
from the web.
Third party links
The Platforms links to other websites/ applications that may collect personally identifiable information
about you. The Company is not and will not be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of
those linked websites. Company does not endorse or make any representations about third-party
websites or services. Company’s Privacy Policy does not cover the information you choose to provide to
or that is collected by these third parties. Company strongly encourage you to read such third parties’
privacy policies.
Advertisements
Company may use third-party advertising companies/ entities to serve ads when you visit Company’s
Platforms. These entities may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or
telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about
goods and services of interest to you.
Data protection
Company have implemented technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal and
commercial information from accidental loss and unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure.
However, no method of transmission over the internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic
storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Company strives to use commercially acceptable means to
protect your personal information, Company cannot guarantee its absolute security. You hereby

acknowledge and accept that providing personal and commercial information is at your own risk and that
the Company will not be held liable for any losses or damages incurred.
Notwithstanding anything contained herein, Company shall not be liable or responsible for disclosure of
your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond
Company’s control or force measure or hacking. You should not share your user name, password, or other
security information for your account with anyone. If Company receive instructions using your user name
and password, Company will consider that you have authorized the instructions.
Amendments to this privacy policy
Company reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the law,
Company’s data collection and use practices, the features of Company’s services, or advances in
technology. Please check this page periodically for changes. Use of information Company collect is subject
to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If Company make any material changes
to this Privacy Policy, Company will post the changes here. Please review the changes carefully. Your
continued use of the Services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your
consent and acceptance of those changes.
Grievance Officer
In case of any Grievances, please feel free to reach out to the Grievance Office
North                                                 East                                            Zone
Mr.                                Asit                            Kumar                             Pathy
Guwahati
9435124216
asitp@godrej.com
East                                                                                                  Zone
Mr.                                                  Sayan                                              De
Kolkata
9830815760
sayan@godrej.com
Central                                                                                               Zone
Mr.                                            Biswajit                                      Bhattacharya
Bhopal
9431109545
bhatta@godrej.com
North                                                                                                 Zone
Mr.                                                Manish                                            Bhatt
Delhi
9628377888
mbhatt@godrej.com
North                                                 West                                            Zone

Mr.                                             Manoj                                                 Singla
Delhi
9910697608
singla@godrej.com
West                                                                                                   Zone
Mr.                                              Rahul                                                Singh
Mumbai
910344001
rahulks@godrej.com
South                                                                                                  Zone
Mr.                                                P.                                               Karthik
Chennai
9940654298
pkarthik@godrej.com
South                                                                                                  Zone
Mr.                                              Vipin                                               Kumar
Bangalore
8939877756
vipins@godrej.com
Consent from you
By using the Platforms and/ or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the
information you disclose on the Platforms in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited
to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.
If Company decide to change Company’s privacy policy, Company will post those changes on this page so
that you are always aware of what information Company collect, how Company use it, and under what
circumstances Company disclose it.
Jurisdiction and Applicable Law
The laws of India shall govern these Terms of Use and your use of the site, and you irrevocably consent to
the jurisdiction of the courts located in Mumbai for any action arising out of or relating to Company’s
privacy policy.
